peoplekeep.com 2019-08-08

# Privacy Policy

During your visit to our website(s), we automatically collect and store the following information:

  * the IP address you are using to access the Internet,
  * the date and time of your visit,
  * the pages you visited, and
  * the address of the website you came from when you came to visit.

We use [Hotjar](https://www.hotjar.com/) in order to better understand our users’ needs and to optimize this service and experience. Hotjar is a technology service that helps us better understand our users experience (e.g. how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click, what users do and don’t like, etc.) and this enables us to build and maintain our service with user feedback. Hotjar uses cookies and other technologies to collect data on our users’ behavior and their devices (in particular device's IP address (captured and stored only in anonymized form), device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), preferred language used to display our website). Hotjar stores this information in a pseudonymized user profile. Neither Hotjar nor we will ever use this information to identify individual users or to match it with further data on an individual user. For further details, please see Hotjar’s privacy policy by clicking on [this link](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy).

You can opt-out to the creation of a user profile, Hotjar’s storing of data about your usage of our site and Hotjar’s use of tracking cookies on other websites by following this [opt-out link](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/opt-out).

Unless it is specifically stated otherwise, no additional information will be collected about you.

#### Personally provided information

You do not have to give us personal information to visit our websites.

If you choose to provide us with additional information about yourself, we maintain this information until specifically requested by you to delete it or until a reasonable length of time has passed such that the information is no longer needed to serve you.

#### Disclosure

PeopleKeep and its related websites does not disclose, give, sell, or transfer any personal information about our visitors to unrelated third parties, unless required by judicial order or statute. If you supply personal information through an associate or affiliated website, the associate or affiliate may also have access to such information as allowed by law—for example, we do not share protected health information (PHI) with unlicensed affiliates or associates.
